hey guys I'm Anna and today I'm going to
show you how to fix manual life
insurance app not working so first of
all you need to make sure you're running
the latest version of the app open up
app store on your device and then tap on
this search icon in the bottom right
corner then search for the manual life
insurance app and if you see this update
button right next to the app name simply
tap on it to make sure you're running
the latest version of the app but if you
still encounter this issue then you need
to clear app cach
go to your device settings and then
scroll all the way down to General and
tap on it then tap on iPhone storage
from here search for the manual life
insurance app and then tap on it once
you're on this screen you need to tap on
offload app tap again to confirm it'll
take a bit for processing and then a
reinstall button will show up simply tap
on it to reinstall the app this should
fix the issue but if it doesn't then you
need to completely reinstall the app
follow the onscreen instructions to
navigate all the way to the app page
once you're on this screen tap on delete
app to uninstall the app from your
device once uninstalled you need to open
up app store and then search for the
manual life insurance app right over
here in the search bar and then click on
this get button to install it back on
your device hopefully this will fix the
issue and if it did then make sure you
give this video a super thanks by
clicking on this heart icon to help
support the channel and don't forget to
hit that subscribe button we'll we'll
see you in the next one
[Music]